How heavy is this glass of water?
Melissa, would you care to answer?
Um,
8 oz.
12 oz.
16 oz.
The absolute weight
of the glass doesn't matter.
Depends on how long I hold onto it.
If I hold it for a minute, nothing
happens.
If I hold it for an hour, my arm will
begin to ache.
If I hold it all day long, my arm will
feel numb and paralyzed.
Well, the way that the glass hasn't
changed, but the longer I hold on to it,
the heavier it becomes.
The stresses and the worries of life are
like this glass of water.
If you think about them for a little
while, there's no problem.
Think about it for a little bit longer,
it begins to hurt.
You think about them all day long, and
you'll feel paralyzed, incapable of doing
anything.
Always remember
put the glass down.